Guys welcome back to my channel.  I hope
all the brothers are doing well.
Welcome Sushil Goswami Sir.   Thank
you.  Thank you.  Friend, this is my
routine every day.  Wear coat and pants and go
to the college for the interview.  There is an interview today also.
Today the company coming is ICICI Lombard which is a
general insurance company.  Similarly, Chhutli
Mutli company is coming to our college.
So what to do?  I have to sit in the placement.  Every
day has its own routine.  Go give
your interview.  Come to your home, home
leave.  Nothing productive is happening
in my life.   Let's go.
Actually, the time given was 8:00 pm,
but which company comes at 8:00 pm, friend?
I am just going to lie down.  It's 9:00 o'clock.
Now I am leaving, I will take out the car and go to
college.  Brother, there is no fog today.  There is a
nice sunshine today.  The weather is clear today.
Guys what brand is this?  I feel like a pig
and the people who placed the pens also feel like pigs.   You
can also report.
Turn off the cameras.   You
K R J
Guys, they all have come for placement.
All JP's children are standing here.
What have you done to me?   He
's a pig, brother.
Look brother, this is a pig brand.
Hey pig, no
pig.  Wearing this shirt made of pig fat
[laughs]
Hey
guys, there is a fight going on here, fight it, we will let you know as soon as the
camera opens, now you will shake hands,
leave the hands and
stop fighting, guys,
these were all our panelists from ICICI
Lombard, they just gave a presentation on
what are our roles and responsibilities
and what compensation will we get.  Now we will have
GD round.  Brother, his interview is going on.  It has been
several hours since he has been standing.
How long have you been standing?
Brother, it has been 20 minutes since I stood there.
When did the good GD happen?
GD was done in an hour.  So 20 minutes ago I came to know that I have been
selected.   Sit
down.
Children from other colleges have also come.
Interview is going on in this class and in this class.
Guys Vivek is not getting it clearly.
Look Vivek is giving an interview.
I took it home and sat down and watched the guys' interviews etc.   The
result of the interview has not come yet.   It's
quarter to five.  There are still many children living.
He will play it at 7-8.  So I came
home.
However, I was eliminated in the GD round itself.  The
GD round also ended a short while ago.
So I came home.
Personal interview has to be conducted at the office.
Now I am going home.  I will go inside, change and
rest.   Guys,
this boy is learning horse riding
here on the village road.   See see.
Brother, I came home from college after resting for a while
and I came there on the roof of the Kasar tree,
look what a wonderful weather it is, the wind is blowing
nicely, let me enjoy the weather for
a while, ah yes, it is fun,
you guys also enjoy the weather, after
roaming around outside for a while, I have come
home and today's blog
ends here.  If you liked today's blog then
please like, share and subscribe to the channel.  Bye.